Guide to the Cooper, Hewitt & Co. Letterpress Copybooks 1848-1905 MS 1130
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Volume 254, 1900 February-April (Offsite-box 48)
- Volume 255, 1900 April-June (Offsite-box 48)
- Volume 256, 1900 June-September (Offsite-box 49)
- Volume 257, 1900 September-November (Offsite-box 49)
- Volume 258, 1900 November-1901 February (Offsite-box 49)
- Volume 259, 1901 February-April (Offsite-box 49)
- Volume 260, 1901 April-June (Offsite-box 49)
- Volume 261, 1901 June-September (Offsite-box 49)
- Volume 262, 1901 September-November (Offsite-box 50)
- Volume 263, 1901 November-1902 January (Offsite-box 50)
- Volume 264, 1902 January-March (Offsite-box 50)
- Volume 265, 1902 March=June (Offsite-box 50)
- Volume 266, 1902 June-August (Offsite-box 50)
- Volume 267, 1902 August-October (Offsite-box 50)
- Volume 268, 1902 October-1903 January (Offsite-box 51)
- Volume 269, 1903 January-March (Offsite-box 51)
- Volume 270, 1903 March-June (Offsite-box 51)
- Volume 271, 1903 June-1905 April (Offsite-box 51)